Please subscribe to my channel and
follow me on Twitter!
We never imagined that we would perform
in an arena, even though we are not
audience.
We never imagined that we would perform
in an arena, even though we are not
audience.
We were so happy and grateful.
It was so fun.
Time flew by when we started the live.
It was a memorable live.
We saw our new dream.
We were so happy to perform live.
We are happy to perform live.
It is not easy to perform live in a big
venue.
We are happy to perform live with this
precious opportunity.
I hope that the young people will come
to the venue.
It is not easy to get along with them,
but we will do our best.
If we take the steps together with the
young people,
we can see beautiful scenery together.
I am excited.
I thought that I used the stage in a
luxurious way.
It was the first time to use 360
degrees.
I thought that it would be more
comfortable if I used 360 degrees.
I performed live with that in mind.
To be continued...
I'll be on stage in about 15 minutes!
I've done a lot of rehearsals on this
big stage, but the glittering stage is
beautiful and it's so wonderful.
I'll do my best! I'll do my best!
We're about to start the show.
I thought we were going to do it here,
but there were a lot of things to do.
It's not a very common venue, so the
next time we do it is with the
promoters.
Today, we're going to do our best at
the Saitama Super Arena.
I'll do my best! I'll do my best!
How many people are there? It's a
little decided today.
I'm in a good mood. I'll do my best!
I'll do my best! I'll do my best!
It's okay!
The live show will start in 10 minutes.
I was so nervous when I did the
rehearsal.
I'll do my best!
Even if it's not love, even if it's not
a dream
I'll do my best to hit it
If I can learn even one
I'll do my best
Thank you for watching.
I'll always be with you
Let's start.
Let's have fun.
Let's go.
Kanami
Clear
Hitoka
Haruka
Aki
Hiyori
Super-exciting advertisement
Rock'n'Roll
Let's do our best.
Great!
We, Saitama Super 8...
I just got so into it
I'm glad it was me and Tokisen
But on the other hand I just wanted the
overwhelming view ofard
And it must of been a very strengths
360 degrees is for But the eyeball's
flicker
We met something interesting during the
rehearsal
But when we COMPETED in real
competition
The more we dance about it, it livens
up our motivating line.
And it's so much fun to dance and put
our eyes together with the members.
I think it was a great experience.
I learned a lot from the set handler.
We did a lot of things we've never done
before, so I was happy to be on stage.
The center stage is where the set
handler will look at us 360 degrees.
The rehearsal was a little different
from the previous ones.
We met with the members and danced.
I thought it was fresh and fun.
I was happy to see the set handler look
at us 360 degrees and notice our new
charms.
I was glad to see the set handler look
at us 360 degrees.
I was so excited when I heard that we
were going to perform at the Super Arena
in Saitama.
It was a dreamy day.
I was wondering if we could use the
luxury way of using the set handler.
But the staff prepared this space for
us.
I was glad that the staff was telling
us that we were going to be here.
I'm sure we'll be here.
I'm going to come back with a smile
with Senrenmei.
How was it?
Rock on!
We are Super Sakimei Senren!
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for your hard work.
It was fun.
We finished the live performance of
HITOMUSU.
Did you enjoy today's live performance?
I really wanted to come back to this
stage with you again.
I'm...
I was really happy.
This time, this time to be able to
perform live like this is a very
important time for me.
I've always wanted this kind of time to
continue.
I hope that the day will come when I
can create the best scenery with you
again.
I want to keep moving forward.
Please continue to support me.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for watching today.
I have been on the stage of Saitama
Super Arena as a promotional act before.
I was very happy to be back on the
stage as a promotional act again.
But I felt a little lonely when I saw
the seats where the promotional act was
not.
I thought I loved everyone again.
I thought everyone's presence was very
big among us.
I really wanted to come back to Saitama
Super Arena and have a live performance.
I hope everyone who watched today will
make their dreams come true and meet
with the same smile.
Let's dye the venue orange!
Thank you very much.
I'm sad that I can't meet you, but I'm
looking forward to seeing you again.
Thank you very much.
I can't meet you now, but I'm always
grateful to the fans who support me on
live broadcast.
Thank you always.
I'm looking forward to seeing beautiful
scenery with you when I can meet you.
Thank you always for meeting me soon.
How are you doing, everyone?
I'm really sad that I can't see you.
Even now, when we can't meet, many fans
send us messages on blog, twitter, and
A-L-E-R.
They send us e-mails when we are on the
radio.
Even when we can't meet in person, we
are doing our best because of your
support.
I want to say thank you to you when we
meet again.
I think it's time to do our best. I
believe that we can have more fun days
if we overcome this.
I hope you don't forget us even in this
period.
We will never forget you. Thank you.
Thank you for watching us.
We will be on the center stage of
Saitama Super Arena.
I thought that if we can do a super
popular ad, we can come back here with
the ad.
I hope we can make our dream come true
together.
I hope you will support us.
When I sing the lyrics of BEAUTY, I
sing the lyrics of the song.
I'm so happy that I can be so absorbed
in TokiSEN.
I will keep TokiSEN in my heart.
I will do my best to be the best of
you.
Thank you for watching us.
Please subscribe to my channel!
Yes.
The answer is...
Yes!
I'll do it.
Wow!
Really?
Please subscribe to my channel!
You're not coming back here anymore,
are you?
I did my best, I did my best, I was
able to say
Stay a little longer, a little longer
by my side
I love you, I love you
Hey, I'll never, never forget
Under the sky that opened up
I love you, I love you
I'll definitely come back to Saitama
Super Arena!
Benji! One, two, six, nine!